You've got a top notch group investigating A.I. What are they up to. What's the next level of finance you think A.I. can
unlock. Yeah I think the most important thing is that it's A.I. is real. We already have thousands of people doing it. Top
scientists around the world. Manuel Veloso from who ran Carnegie Mellon machine learning is a living breathing thing. So
people want to ask what's going to do. It's a living breathing thing. It's going to change. They're going to be all different
types of models and different types of tools and technology. But the way to think about for us is every single process. So
errors trading hedging research every app every database you can be applying A.I. so might be as a co-pilot. It might be to
replace humans. You know A.I. is doing all the equity hedging for us. For the most part it's idea generation is large
language models. It's note taking while you're talking to someone and most taking notes and actually say to you that here's
the thing of interest the client might be interested in all error all customer service. It's a little bit of everything. But it is
going to replace some jobs. Of course. Yeah. But I look folks people have to take a deep breath. OK. Technologies over always
replace jobs. Your children live to 100 and not have cancer because of technology. And literally they'll probably be working
three and a half days a week. So technology has done unbelievable things for mankind. But you know planes crash.
Pharmacists get misused. There are negatives. This one the biggest negative in my view is A.I. being used by bad people to do
bad things. Think of cyber. You know Henry Kissinger talks about warfare. But you know the fact and I do think you know
eventually have legal guardrails around. It's kind of hard to do because it's new but it will add a huge value. And you know for
JP Morgan if it replaces jobs you know we hope to redeploy people.